internetworldstats.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy and Disclaimers - Internet World Stats

> **5 - THIRD PARTY COOKIES**
> 
> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
> 
>   
>  **^ return to index**  
>    
> 
> 
> * * *  
  
---  
  
> **6 - LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**
> 
> Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under the control of Miniwatts. Miniwatts shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. Miniwatts does not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the Site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the Site, you do so entirely at your own risk.
> 
>   
>  **7 - CHILDREN'S PRIVACY  
>  **   
>  Miniwatts cares about the safety of children and their use of the Internet. Therefore, in accordance with the [Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998](http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm), we will never knowingly request or solicit personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. In the event that we receive actual knowledge that we have collected such personal information without the requisite and verifiable parental consent, we will delete that information from our database as quickly as is practicable.  
> 
> 
>   
>  **8 - OPTING-OUT** We respect your privacy and ability to choose whether to share information with us and any third party. You may choose to "opt-out" of subscriptions, or sharing Personal Information in several ways. You may choose to be contacted by any or all of these methods, or "opt-out" by sending an email to any of our contact options. You may change your contact options at any time by following the process described in "Reviewing, Changing, and Deleting Your Personal Information."
> 
> You may "opt-out" altogether from providing Personal Information to us by not registering on the Site, nor registering for any Site sponsored promotion, and thereby not providing your Personal Information. You may also choose at a later date to have your name removed from our database by deleting your subscription registration profile. To do so, please follow the process described in "Reviewing, Changing, and Deleting Your Personal Information."
> 
> Certain portions of the Site and certain services provided on the Site, however, do require registration in order to access or use these areas and services. If you choose not to register or provide certain information, these areas will not be accessible to you.
> 
>   
>  **^ return to index**  
>    
>   
  
> **9 - REVIEWING, CHANGING AND DELETING YOUR INFORMATION** You may request a review of the Personal Information that we collect from you online and maintain by sending an email request. See below "contacting us" for the contact form.
> 
> For changing, or deleting (unsubscribing) please follow this same the procedure. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access, making corrections, or deleting information.
> 
>   
>  **^ return to index**  
>    
>   
  
> **10 - SECURITY** Miniwatts maintains industry standard safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of the Personal Information that you provide to the Miniwatts Marketing Group.  
>   
  
For complaints, please send an email to:  
_" abuse @ internetworldstats.com "_

> **^ return to index**  
  
> * * *
> 
>   
>  **12 - REPRODUCTION OF THE STATISTICS**  
>  The content of this website is intellectual property of its owner Enrique de Argaez and/or Miniwatts de Colombia Ltda. Data from this web site may be cited freely, giving due credit to the original data sources and establishing an active link back to [ www.internetworldstats.com](https://www.internetworldstats.com/). A notice of publication will be greatly appreciated, and might be rewarded with a reciprocal link from IWS back to your website.
> 
> Use of our content for commercial purposes requires a permission. For details, please read the
> 
> [ Copyrights](https://www.internetworldstats.com/copyrights.htm) page.
> 
> **DISCLAIMER**  
>  Most of the data in this web site comes from independent sources, found displayed freely in the wide world web. Other data has been investigated and retrieved directly by our staff. All the information has been consolidated by IWS, giving due credit to the corresponding original sources when these are known, and establishing a link back if possible. IWS provides and publishes the data and displays statistics in good faith but does not guarantee the accuracy or provenience. Likewise Miniwatts is not responsible for the use given to this information. The usage and population data are the best estimates available at the moment of publishing, and a reasonable margin of error should be allowed for, as is usual for all statistical work.
> 
> In the event that any owner of the information cited or the sources cited oppose the publication of specific data, please let us know by advising our webmaster ("webmaster" at "@" "internetworldstats.com"). We will promptly remove said data from our web site.
> 
> Visitors please take note that for statistical purposes Mexico has been included in the Central American countries statistics, according to the
> 
> [United Nations Statistics Division](https://unstats.un.org/unsd/methods/m49/m49regin.htm) methods and classifications of macro geographical (continental) regions, geographical sub-regions, and selected economic and other groupings. Turkey is included in the European statistics.
> 
> The designations employed and the presentation of material at this site do not imply the expression of any opinion whatsoever on our part concerning the legal status of any country, territory, city or area or of its authorities, or concerning the delimitation of its frontiers or boundaries. The assignment of countries or areas to specific groupings is for statistical convenience and does not imply any assumption regarding political or other affiliation of countries or territories by the United Nations or by this web site.  
  
>   
>    
>  **13 - EFFECTIVE DATE AND CHANGES**  
>  This Privacy Policy is effective as of May 31, 2019. Miniwatts reserves the  
>  right to modify the terms of this policy at any time and in our sole discretion,  
>  by posting a change notice to this page. Your continued use of this Web Site  
>  following our posting of a change notice will constitute binding acceptance of  
>  those changes.  
> 
> 
> **^ return to index**
> 
> * * *
